♪ Wonderful electric ♪
♪ Cover me in you ♪
Woo!
♪ I'm in love ♪
♪ I'm in love with a strict machine ♪
- ♪ I'm in love ♪
- Fuck, yeah! Come on!
♪ I'm in love ♪
♪ I'm in love with a strict machine ♪
♪ I'm in love, I'm in love ♪
♪ I'm in love with a sick machine ♪
♪ I'm in love... ♪
I didn't see him, Mia.
Fuck!
Fucking hell, man.
Rob, we've gotta go and look.
- Oh, my gosh, Rob.
- Hey.
It's all right, baby.
Oh, my God...
- Fucking...
- Oh, my God!
Fuck.
Rob, we've gotta call someone.
No, no, no, no, no, no. Fucking
hell, Mia. Think, OK, hey?
You need to think, baby.
- We've been fucking caning it, yeah?
- Yeah.
And I...
This is prison, yeah? A
fucking instant prison.
I've got fuck knows how much
drink in me, I fucking hit a guy.
Now, they will put me in the
cell. I'm the driver, they'll fu...
They'll put me in a cell
and fucking keep me there.
- That's what they'll fucking...
- We can't just leave him here.
- Shut the fuck up, Mia! Shut...
- And just leave him here in the road?!
- I need to fucking think, OK?
- I need to think.
Fuck!
OK, there's, there's a lake over there.
And there's a sleeping bag in the
boot. You keep an eye on the road!
- No.
- Keep an eye on the road!
No.
No!
- Mia.
- Don't.
Mia, come on. Get the
bag with me. Get the bag.
- No. No, get off.
- Baby, come on.
Fuck.
You get the fucking
rocks, I'll stack them, OK?
I need more fucking rocks.
Just put a pile, put
the fucking pile there.
Put the pile...
Close it up. Close it up.
Close his head. Close his head.
Three...
two...
one.
Um, it's an honor to
be speaking here today
amongst such impressive company.
Uh, I'm thrilled to have been shared...
I'm thrilled to have been asked
to share my vision of
the future, such as it is.
Looking around at a world
of injustice, intolerance
and huge environmental challenges,
it's hard to imagine a bright
future, but we can and we must.
It's the only way that we
can build a better tomorrow.
Um...
So I'll start with a funny story.
Right. I'm off.
Bye-bye.
- See you later on.
- See you tomorrow.
OK.
- Have a nice day.
- You too.
- Bye, Mom!
- There we go.
Hiya, puppy.
One moment.
Coming!
Just a second!
- Mrs. Carmichael?
- Yes?
I'm here on behalf of Realm Insurance.
Just need to log your
recollections about the accident.
- Am I all right to come in?
- Uh, OK then.
Someone who has risen to become
one of the most innovative
architects of her generation.
Not just an architect of
buildings, but communities.
But enough of me telling you about
her. Please welcome Mia Nolan.
Thank you, Martin. Thanks. It's
an honor to be speaking here
amongst such impressive company.
Good evening, welcome to Fences Pizza.
Your pizza is ready for collection.
Hello?
- It's me.
- Hey. Hey.
- Did your chin catch Dutch fur disease?
- Yeah, fuck you.
I didn't say I didn't like it. Come in.
What's it been? It's been
like two years now, hasn't it?
Uh, three.
Dropping in on my hotel
room, it must be important.
- Shall we find somewhere to eat?
- Yeah, well, I...
I got in touch 'cause I
saw that you were in town
for what is it, some,
some architecture thing?
It's a forum, they call it.
People actually pay to
come and listen to me talk.
Imagine that.
Almost does my head in.
And you're looking
good. Is that the gym?
Well, you look...
I look like dog shit, Mia.
I'll save you the bother.
Dried-up dog shit.
- Do you want a drink?
- I knocked it on the head.
What, you quit, like fully quit?
Nine months, three weeks, two days.
Well done. Well, that's great.
You go ahead.
- Really, go on.
- You sure?
- Absolutely.
- OK.
You picked a terrible place
to come see me 'cause it reeks of hops
all the way down the
street outside here.
- Did you notice that?
- No.
It's like a full-on beer smell.
Can't help your sobriety, that.
But I probably shouldn't be
talking about booze, should I?
Rob, I hope you're not
here to talk about what I...
It's about that, yeah.
I've been thinking about
it again, that night.
- Rob.
- I can't not think about it.
We said that we'd put
it out of our minds.
Weren't we just gonna
try and keep it out?
I can't. I'm sorry.
It was a long time ago.
Well, in here, it's now.
Yeah, I know.
Why today? Why is it
preying on your mind today?
- There's a news story.
- A news story?
Uh, a featured article.
Well, whatever you call it.
I printed it for you.
Mia?
That... That's her. It's his wife.
- You don't know that's his wife.
- There is a photo of him at the bottom.
It's him.
And the poor cunt, they never found him.
So she never remarried.
She never fucking moved house.
She stayed where she
is in case he came back.
All this time, Mia, she's
still waiting for him.
That's dreadful. But what can we do?
I'm gonna write her a letter.
- No.
- Anonymous.
- I am not gonna mention you.
- Rob, no.
You'll open up God knows what,
you'll just rake it all up.
- I can't live with it, Mia.
- There's things they can do.
'Cause they can trace it back.
They can trace it. They'll
find the body, they'll find us.
- They won't find us.
- Yes, they will, then we're fucked.
Look, when I quit alcohol,
they told me to make amends
with anyone I've ever hurt.
Who have I hurt more than her?
Also say you're not supposed to
hurt anyone else. What about me?
- What about her?
- No, no, no.
No.
No! Fuck!
It was your idea. It
was your fucking idea!
I know. I know, and I'm sorry.
Fifteen years, 15 years, the
fucking shame, the fucking guilt!
I've got somewhere. I've got a life.
You don't know, don't understand.
That's not the point, though.
You don't understand.
You're not married. I've got
a son. He's nine years old.
You've seen photos of
him. Think of him, please.
I'm sorry.
I sat on this for you.
- I fucking sat on this for you!
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
Hey, look at me.
Look at me.
I've made up my mind,
and that's how it is.
Please, please, please.
Please, please, please, Rob. Hey,
listen, I understand. I understand.
Do you?
Yeah. Come on, let's talk about this.
No, no, I can't stay here.
- No, no, no, no.
- What are you doing? Let go!
Mia, I'm fucking leaving.
What are you doing?
Mia, let the... Mia, let the
fuck... Let the fuck... go!
Fuck...
Ah!
Huh?
Codger.
That's his name, Codger.
What?
- Ah, you don't like him.
- Oh, it's not that.
- It's so hard to get presents for you.
- No, I like him. He's... fluffy.
Exactly. No, Ali's gonna love him.
It's just we've got a lot
going on, what with Ali and...
I'll take him back. The pet shop
guy was OK. It won't be a problem.
No, no, no, no, you're
right. It'll be good for Ali.
Codger stays.
He's... Codger the lodger.
Changing time. Uh...
- Happy birthday.
- Thanks.
Room service.
Lovely, thank you.
Hi. Hiya, love.
Yeah, it was... No,
the speech went great.
Yeah, I'm back in the morning.
I'm just tired, that's all.
Um...
Did he? Oh, that's great.
No, don't put him on.
Hi, hey.
Hey, Dad said you were great
in your rehearsal for your play.
You had a good rehearsal?
Yeah, I'm proud of you.
Yeah.
I love you.
So that's one night.
You had room service and a
ã9.99 charge for the movie.
For a movie?
You... you watched
a film last night, no?
Yeah. I was in last night, yeah.
Thanks.
Thank you.
I'm from Realm Insurance,
about the pizza van accident.
Oh, come in.
I mean,
it'll cover you for up to four months,
but that is quite a substantial claim.
Well, I was heading off on tour
with the Philharmonic next week.
Europe, Middle East, Australia.
- Not now.
- Mm.
As I'm sure you appreciate,
with a payout of this size,
- we will need to investigate the accident.
- Yeah, of course.
Now, that stretch of the street
has a security camera, vandalized,
by some kids, I'm guessing,
paintballed right in the wrong place.
But the, um...
delivery van thing must've had a camera.
- Not working.
- Oh, for God's sake.
No, that's actually good for your
claim. Fences Pizza's a big company.
They've been claiming their
driverless fleet has a good record.
The malfunctioning camera,
that's a step toward negligence.
So if we can prove full liability,
you could also consider filing
a substantial civil case
under our litigation wing?
Could be a lot of money.
Yeah, OK, I'm sold.
Great.
Now, I'll just hook you up
to the recaller here.
It's one of those memory dredgers?
We prefer "corroborators."
- Police things, aren't they?
- Mm... Not since last year.
We all have them now.
Right.
- May I?
- Yeah.
I feel like a specimen.
So, this accesses engrams,
your memories of what happened.
Now, they're subjective.
They may not be totally accurate,
and they're often emotional,
but by collecting a
range of recollections
from yourself and any witnesses,
we can help build a corroborative
picture of the whole.
I don't remember anything.
It's a total blank.
Oh, I've got something that might help.
What, getting drunk?
The accident happened
a few hundred meters from
the Castle Port Brewery.
The whole area smells like a pub.
No sipping, just take a sniff.
Aroma's a great memory
boost, helps anchor you
to where you were.
Oh... that's familiar.
OK. Now, hold that smell in your mind,
close your eyes and picture the street.
Getting something now.
Yeah. I went to a sort of comic shop...
Culty stuff. Um...
I think it started
snowing when I came out.
Heavy snow, um...
There was music from a car.
I like that song.
There was a woman in a
yellow coat coming towards me.
Good recall on her face.
She had this weird
lipstick on. It stood out.
And she's pretty.
Um, yeah, yeah, and that, too.
Well, the more emotional your response,
the more vivid your memory of it is.
So there was the music and a
girl, and then what happened?
Well, I went to cross the road,
wasn't really thinking about anything,
and, uh...
And that's just when it just goes. Um...
That's OK. What you've
given me is already useful.
Really?
Well, I've got someone to look
for, Little Miss Yellow Coat.
- Hey.
- Ah, the wanderer returns.
- Yeah.
- You don't know how to fix this, do you?
Um, yeah, I'll have a look at it later.
- Hi, Mom.
- Hi, you.
Tonight's the big night.
♪ We coulda been anything ♪
♪ That we wanted to be ♪
Dad!
School musical, Bugsy Malone.
You all right?
Yeah. Yeah.
They've got this, um, sound
system for the backing tracks
that they can't work out
and I said I'd help them out.
So... I'm gonna be there all day.
You're gonna die of
loneliness here, are you?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Well, we'll see you later, 7:30.
- Mm-hmm.
- Don't forget.
I won't.
- See ya.
- See you later.
Bye.
It was only yesterday. You're efficient.
The fresher the memory,
the stronger it is,
and the stronger the memory,
the stronger the case.
I'll also just get you
to take a sniff of this.
God knows what they
think we're doing in here.
If you close your eyes, I'm
also gonna play a piece of music.
God, yeah, yeah, that, that was on.
How weird.
Hold those things in your
mind and picture what you saw.
I was on Stanhope Road,
near the hotel place,
looking at flats and stuff,
you know, window shopping.
I saw this guy walking towards me.
I remember thinking he
looked sort of sweet.
The music was coming from
the car, which pulled off.
Actually that was when the
delivery thing drove past.
Fences Pizza? What sort
of speed was it going?
You mean, was it going too fast?
Um...
- Try and focus on the vehicle.
- Maybe.
Um...
I don't know. I couldn't really say.
What about the impact itself?
Well, I didn't really see it. I
just saw the aftermath, really.
A moment earlier you saw a bright light?
Yeah. Like a camera flash just before.
Just outside the dentist place.
Hmm.
And I'm assuming your
window glazing's soundproof.
- Yes, we get the odd screamer.
- I won't bother with the music then.
Look, to be honest, the
memory's a bit embarrassing...
- Don't worry, I've seen it all.
- Do you have to use that thing?
Look, your memories will
be sealed and private.
Unless they indicate you're
harming yourself or another person.
Go on then.
I'd had a patient.
Hmm, so I see.
She left around six, I think.
I stayed to clear up.
You saw something from the window?
There was a guy in the hotel window.
Well, what can I say?
He was picturesque.
Did you take a photo?
Well, I tried to.
I left the flash on by mistake,
so all I got was the reflection.
- And then?
- I was going to take another one.
I saw some woman staring at something.
So I looked down, it was
just a load of commotion.
There was a woman in
a sort of lime coat.
Hmm, yellow actually.
- Well, I knew it was vivid.
- Well, memories can be subjective.
What we do is build
up an overall average,
a crowd-sourced picture of reality.
Did you see the vehicle
that hit the pedestrian?
Any sense of its speed?
I didn't see the actual crash, sorry.
OK.
You won't tell anyone about the photo?
Don't need to put that in my report.
It's safe with me.
That'd be room 304.
Can you tell me who stayed there?
- You're not the police?
- No, but...
Then you'd have to lodge for
an information request for that.
But that could take up
to a week to process.
Sorry, management's an ass
about it ever since that thing
with what's-his-name,
the judge of Hot Shots?
Anyway, he got caught with a rent
boy and, um, a tabloid got his name
by hacking our booking system, and yeah,
they're tight as anything
about the rule now.
Oh, the woman I'm after
hasn't done anything.
I just think she might
have seen something outside
yesterday evening about 6:30.
Oh, I can...
I can tell you that
she wasn't outside...
and I know what she was looking at.
How so?
I can't tell you who she is but,
um, she's into interesting films.
We log the in-house movies
that people watch and, um...
her choice stood out.
Oh.
How nice for her. Thanks.
Oh, bless you.
How's the pizza accident going?
Hmm. A pain in the ass.
Can't pinpoint liability
'cause no one agrees on the
speed of the bloody thing
and I can't find anyone
who actually saw the impact.
Well, not yet.
Except maybe smudge face
here, whoever she is.
Oh, bingo.
Mia Nolan. You might be
the one, if you'll talk.
What, if she'll talk?
She was doing something
embarrassing in the hotel room,
watching a porn film.
She might not want me
poking around in her head.
She's, like, 50 miles out of town.
Do you mind if I head there now?
It's a bit late.
Oh, if I sew this up in 24
hours, I get two times bonus.
Well...
Go. Go.
♪ I know I won't ever let you go ♪
♪ Oh, it's more than I could ever stand ♪
♪ Oh, but anyone ♪
♪ Who knows what love is ♪
♪ Will understand ♪
Hi, I'm Shazia. I'm
from Realm Insurance.
- I've already got insurance, thanks.
- I'm not selling anything.
I'm following up on an incident
you might've seen, a road accident.
I don't know anything about an accident.
This was only yesterday.
- An accident?
- On Stanhope Road.
Medina Plaza Hotel, a pedestrian
was hit by a delivery vehicle,
Fences Pizza, driverless.
Um...
Right, yeah. I'm sorry, actually I did.
When you first mentioned it,
I just didn't think of
it, but um... yeah, I did.
So you saw what happened?
Uh, yeah, there was a
guy crossing the street
and this little van thing sort
of just clipped him, it was quick.
Do you mind if I ask you
a few questions about it?
It won't take long.
I'm sorry, I'm really busy. I've got...
I don't wanna sound heavy
but it's a legal
requirement since last year.
It's a legal requirement?
Well, if you've witnessed
an incident, yes.
I have to notify the
police when people refuse,
and when they get involved, it
just drags everything out, so...
- Come in.
- Thank you.
Yeah, just that way.
OK.
- What does that do?
- The recaller?
Just helps me get a
record of what happened.
May I?
Well, I can just tell you
what happened. I can remember.
The van hit the guy, and he fell
over, and then people came to help.
How fast was it going
though, the delivery vehicle?
Um...
See, I just need a sense of that.
It's sometimes hard to articulate
what your mind's eye's seen,
but capturing your impression
of what you saw is really useful.
- OK, but I've got...
- And that's all I'm interested in.
You can read the terms here if you like.
All the legal stuff is in there.
Look, I don't care what
you might've been doing
in the hotel room in your own time.
I'm not gonna ask you anything
about that. Won't go there.
- OK.
- Private stuff is private stuff.
- So it's just the accident?
- Just that.
It's a bit of a long read, isn't it?
- Do you want a tea or a coffee?
- Oh, a coffee would be great.
- Yeah, OK. Espresso?
- Perfect.
Do you mind if I just go and have a pee
if I'm gonna be sat down a while?
- Yeah, sure.
- OK.
I ate hotel food, I had room service.
I ate room service.
I was in the hotel room on my own.
Watched porn.
Saw the accident.
Come on, focus.
I was on my own.
There you go.
Take a sniff.
- What's that for?
- It'll just help your recall.
That's it.
The music will help
jog your memory, too.
OK, close your eyes.
OK, let's start with
you in your hotel room.
♪ You can blame me ♪
♪ Try to shame me... ♪
So I was in my room and
I ordered room service.
♪ ... care for you ♪
All I need is the accident.
Try to picture the moments
leading up to the impact.
♪ Anyone ♪
♪ I just feel so sorry ♪
The fucking shame, the fucking guilt...
No.
No!
- I sat on this...
- Get the fuck off me fucking...
Well, that's... great.
Got what I needed on
the van, so, I'll be off.
OK.
That's it.
- So you've got everything you needed?
- Yeah.
Doesn't take long, it's just a
simple thing with the speed so...
- Right.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Sorry about being short,
it's been a long day.
- No, it's fine.
- Got a lot of work on. Did you...
- So you've got everything you needed?
- Yeah, yeah, got it all.
- Don't worry, thank you so much.
- I know this sounds silly,
but, um, you know, sometimes
I just think mad things,
and it doesn't mean anything,
do you know what I mean? When
you have strange thoughts.
No, it's fine, like I said. I
got what I needed, so thank you.
Yeah, but do you know what I mean?
It's not like... it's just my head.
Come on!
No.
No, no, no, no! No!
No!
I'm sorry, um...
Um...
I fucked up, and I panicked.
Does your head hurt?
OK.
What am I gonna do with you?
I mean, I can't let you go.
You're gonna tell someone, aren't you?
I know, but even if you say you won't,
your recollections are all recorded.
- I won't.
- They're not?
No.
If I take that off your mouth,
will you promise not to scream?
Do you promise?
Forget the report. I'll delete...
I'll delete it, it won't go anywhere.
I don't know. I tried to delete
it, and I couldn't figure it out.
I won't say anything to anyone, I
promise. I'll forget the whole thing.
No one will know. I won't say anything.
I wish I believed you.
I mean it. I mean it. I've seen things.
I've seen things on the recaller.
Secrets, personal things,
I've never spilled any of it.
I'm not allowed to, it's the law.
It's like confession, it's
like Catholic confession.
It'll be illegal for me to say anything.
Totally illegal, even if I wanted to!
None of that's true, is it?
- It is, I swear.
- It's not.
It is.
Did you tell anyone that
you were coming here today?
No.
- You're lying.
- I'm not. I swear I'm not lying.
No, I swear.
I swear. No!
No!
What did you do before
you came here today?
♪ Oh, but anyone ♪
♪ Who knows what love is... ♪
I like that song.
♪ Will understand ♪
Who did you speak to?
Bingo.
Mia Nolan, if she'll talk.
- If she'll talk?
- No!
No.
- Is that your husband?
- No!
No!
I'm really sorry.
Will you please close your eyes for me?
Everyone's in their costumes already.
Yeah, please, make sure you're on time.
- Yeah, I know, love.
- Are you far off?
- Remember it starts at 7:30.
- I'm gonna make it, 7:30.
- At 7:30.
- Yeah.
- All right.
- I'll see you outside.
- See you in a bit, sweetheart.
- OK.
- Cutting it a bit fine.
- Yeah, it was just work stuff.
Jesus, what'd you eat, a vineyard?
No, I just finished the
design so had a glass of wine.
- Fuck off, a glass. Fine.
- Let's just go in, all right?
♪ We coulda been anything ♪
♪ That we wanted to be ♪
♪ And it's not too late to change ♪
♪ It's been decided ♪
♪ To give it some thought ♪
♪ Maybe you'll agree we really ought ♪
♪ Two, three, four! ♪
♪ We coulda been anything ♪
♪ That we wanted to be ♪
♪ Yes, that decision was ours ♪
♪ It's been decided we're weaker divided ♪
♪ Let friendship double up our powers ♪
Yeah, just confirming double homicide.
One adult male and one male infant.
Yeah, I'm at the scene now.
Who kills a baby?
I don't know.
Probably someone worried
about leaving a witness.
Bloodbath upstairs and this downstairs.
But he couldn't see.
Poor fucker was born blind apparently.
So I have to say, I have absolutely
no idea who I'm looking for.
So it's a good job you're not asking me.
Come on, let's clear out of here.
Let's let the recall team do their job.
Come on.
Here we go.
♪ You give a little love ♪
♪ And it all comes back to you ♪
♪ La la la la la la la ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ You're gonna be remembered ♪
♪ For the things that you say and do ♪
- Well done!
- Put your hands together
for this year's fantastic school choir.
What a lovely evening.
Thank you so much for coming.
Put your hands together
for Mrs. Henry...
Bravo! Yay!
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -