- Coach.
- Yes, Frank?
- Where do I go?
- Proceed to the hub.
Got ya.
- How will I know who he is?
- This is him.
Hi. Oh, oh.
Sorry. Fork.
- Amy.
- No, no, my name's not fork.
- I guessed. It was just...
- It's Frank.
- Do you wanna sit? Shall we sit?
- I think it's that or stand.
Come sit, yeah?
Oh, oh! That's, um...
I was on that side.
- Oh. Shall I... ?
- No, no, it doesn't matter.
Why bring it up?
Sorry. I'm so bloody nervous.
It's my first time on
the, you know, the system.
- Me too.
- Oh, really?
Yeah, I'm shitting it, mate.
- Come to mention it, you look terrified.
- Do I?
- Yeah, quaking with fear.
- Or maybe shaking with revulsion?
At least you stopped... shitting.
Oh!
Are you sure about that?
- Shall we stop talking about shitting?
- Maybe order some food? Good plan.
Yeah. OK.
- Do you know how we order?
- I think we use these.
- Oh!
- Menu choice already established.
- Oh. Ta.
- Here you are, sir.
And for you, madam.
Well, evidently I'm a pasta girl.
Yeah, I'm a, uh...
... fishcake...
- Hmm.
- Mmm.
- It's good.
- Can I try some?
Are we... allowed to do that?
Fuck it.
Yeah, fuck it.
- Mm. That is good.
- Mm-hmm.
So... we're both first-timers.
Hmm.
- Shall we check our expiry date?
- Yeah, good plan.
Yeah? All right, um, so
I think it's under "info."
Yeah, uh, "tap to reveal." We have
to tap to reveal at the same time.
OK. So, on three, two, one. Go.
- Twelve hours.
- Yeah, 12 hours.
- OK.
- Bit, um...
- Yeah.
- Bit short.
- It is a bit short, isn't it?
- Hmm.
Oh. And getting shorter.
I didn't realize it would...
sort of count down like that.
It's sort of sad.
Maybe we should eat quickly.
- Yeah. Yeah, maybe we should.
- The race is on.
Come on, hurry up.
I guess this is us.
And this takes us to the place?
Yeah, suppose so.
- After you.
- Thank you.
It's massive.
- Here we are.
- Yep.
Huh.
- Do you wanna open it or shall I?
- You go ahead.
- All right.
- Ha! Too slow.
You're a knob.
Oh, God. It's a shithole.
- You're kidding.
- I am, yeah.
Ooh!
It's nice. I, uh, like that lamp.
- Yeah, it's incredible, that lamp.
- Fuck off.
Hmm.
Right. That's, uh...
There's an en suite.
- Shower or bath?
- Both.
Ah. That's good.
Uh. Well, I'm... I'm
just gonna use the loo.
Yeah, I've got to,
uh... over here, so...
Yeah.
OK, seriously, what are we meant to do?
Query too broad. Please narrow.
Well, I mean, are we just meant to...
I don't know, like, just go at it?
Define "go at it."
Fucking hell.
So, are we meant to just
have sex with each other?
Participants are not required
to take any specific action.
Yeah, but I mean we can, right?
I mean, people do if
it's just a short time?
If that's your decision.
- It's up to us?
- It's up to you.
I could just sleep here.
Don't be daft. You'll be
scrunched up in a ball.
It's not awful.
The bed's pretty big. I'm
sure we could both fit in it.
Yeah, OK.
Must have been mental before the system.
How do you mean?
Well, people had to do the whole
relationship thing themselves,
work out who they wanna be with.
Hmm. Option paralysis.
So many choices, you end up
not knowing which one you want.
Yeah, exactly, and
if things seem shitty,
they'd have to figure out whether
they wanted to break up with someone.
How to break up with
someone. Fuckin' hell.
- Just a nightmare.
- It's not like when it's all mapped out.
God, no. It's so much simpler
when it's all mapped out.
Hmm.
- This is weird, though.
- It really is. Hmm.
- Well, then.
- So...
Thanks for being my first.
Oh. Yeah.
Bloody time.
It was great, you know. You were nice.
So were you.
If we had this time again, you
would totally get it, by the way.
- Oh, you... You bastard.
- Sorry.
- You'd get it, too.
- Fucked that one up, didn't we?
Yeah, totally.
I guess I just don't see the point
in something that short. Twelve hours.
Even your reaction to a brief encounter
provides the system with
valuable information.
Yeah, well, I didn't even do anything.
The system thinks I'm a prude.
The system makes no moral judgments.
Yeah, but how do I know
she wasn't the perfect
match for me? She was...
Your ultimate compatible other
has not yet been selected.
Yeah, I know, but it's...
The system gains insight as
each participant progresses
through numerous relationships
and uses the gathered data
to eventually select an
ultimate compatible other.
On your pairing day, I know, and
it always finds your perfect match.
In 99.8% of cases.
But I have to go through loads
of relationships to find it.
- That is correct.
- Great.
What was that?
- Another relationship.
- What, already?
What's this, another one?
That is correct.
I'd best go get changed, then.
Holy fuck. Tell me that's him.
I cannot confirm identity
until a personal introduction is made.
- Hi.
Identity confirmed.
- I like your hair.
- Yours is good too.
It's all my own.
It's just funny.
Hi.
I'm Frank.
Hmm.
Nicola. I've been here a while.
Aye, sorry. I was getting changed.
- Really?
- You started already?
- I was hungry.
- Yeah, course, yeah. Sorry.
Come on, let's get it over
with. Checking the expiry.
Oh! Yeah, yeah.
One year.
We've got each other for
one year? Could be a mistake.
- Coach, is this a mistake?
- This is not a mistake.
Jesus fucking Christ.
There'll be a reason.
Thanks.
Look on the bright side.
Chicken tikka masala.
What?
Chicken tikka mas... It's a joke.
Right. So you're the sort
of person that makes jokes.
- OK, so on three.
- Two, one.
Oh. Interesting.
Nine months.
Well... cheers.
Cheers.
Pretty much the same as my last one.
- How many of these have you had?
- Relationships? So far? Five.
- Oh.
- I'm an old hand, I suppose.
Listen, I'm just gonna
jump in the shower.
- OK.
- Won't be long.
Hey.
Hi.
So, listen, if you're OK with it,
this is relationship five for me,
and I've found it's best to
have sex straight away upfront.
Right, yeah.
Kind of breaks the ice,
gives an early overview
of compatibility and so on.
Yep.
So I'm consenting to everything now.
Whenever you feel
comfortable doing the same...
Tikka masala. Just...
- What?
- It's a bit tikka masala.
- Oh. I'm sorry.
- Talking makes it worse.
Sorry.
No, no, you're gonna
have to do it from behind.
- You what?
- From behind.
Bit faster?
More motion.
Not like that. More motion.
You're all in out, in out,
like you're trying to shut a
drawer into a filing cabinet.
- Sorry.
- It's just boring.
Want a bit more side to side.
Like this?
No, not really.
What was that?
- Nothing.
- Hmm.
Fucking hell.
So I can't just walk away?
That is correct.
One day it will provide
you with the ultimate match.
One day. One day.
So I'd just like to say,
do have faith in the system,
because it does deliver.
It did for us.
You have so many experiences,
and then one day it pairs you
up with your ultimate match,
the best in show, as it were.
Ha.
So if you're having doubts,
just hang on in there.
Because it really does work.
Garlic dip. Thanks for that.
- Hi. Hi.
- Mm!
Was that, uh, your... ?
- Yeah. Nicola.
- Oh. Nicola.
- Hmm.
- Ha.
You OK?
No, you're not being...
Oh, my God. OK, this is
happening. OK, um, just...
Oh. Thanks.
- You look well.
- Thanks.
I'd return the compliment, but you've
just spat food on my shoe, so...
To be fair, it is a
revolting shoe, so...
All the better to kick you with.
Was that really hard?
- Ouch.
- I'm so sorry. Fuck.
Shit.
Oh. Oh! Um... Uh...
Lenny, this is, um, Frank.
Frank, this is Lenny.
- Hi, Lenny. You all right?
- Hi.
We were together for a bit.
- A small... small bit.
- Yeah, just before we...
So you two... ? Oh.
That's... that's great.
So, I mean... it looks like
you two make a great team.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Um, I'll see you.
Yeah.
- You know that noise you make?
- What noise?
- Do I do that?
- Yeah, you do, quite often.
Does it bother you?
A bit, yeah.
- I'll try not to.
- OK.
So it's been great, really.
- Shame it has to end.
- But end it must.
Anyway...
OK, bye.
Another partner already?
That is correct.
So, three, two, one, go.
Thirty-six hours?
Well, uh... bye.
- Bye.
Three, two, one.
- I just wanna say...
- Don't.
Well, I learned what it's like
to cohabit with someone I despise.
- Is that useful for the system?
- Everything happens for a reason.
That's sooner than I expected.
- Hello, you.
- Hi.
Hi.
Is this right?
- Yeah.
- I mean...
Yeah, I didn't think the
system would hook us up again.
No, me neither. I mean, I hope
it's right, obviously, but...
- Coach, are we sat at the right table?
- Yes, that is correct.
OK, well...
Wait, um... Can we not
check the expiry date?
- Uh... Why?
- Just sick of it.
The system's just bounced
me from bloke to bloke,
short fling after short fling.
I know they're short flings,
they're just meaningless,
and I get really detached.
It's like I'm not really there.
So the other week, I was with this guy,
God knows who, basically just a haircut.
And I literally had this
out-of-body experience.
I wandered out of my body, and I
sat in this chair across the room
and I watched myself fucking this guy.
And I was, like, what is that all about?
That is literally just a dick
going in and out of a hole.
Yeah, that's pretty detached.
When it's a long-term
thing, it's just as bad,
watching the clock
like you're a prisoner,
counting the hours, the minutes.
- Oh, God, I've been there.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, let's not check the expiry, then.
- It's a deal.
- Deal.
- OK.
- Bring on les fishcake.
I don't know.
- So?
- So...
- Might as well.
- I suppose we have to.
- Don't know how much time we've got.
- Yeah, it could be ten minutes.
- Think you could last ten minutes?
- Fuck off.
All right. OK, then.
Wait. One of us should
get undressed first.
- Why only one of us?
- It'll be funny.
Go on then. Get your kit off.
No. No, it was my idea.
All right.
This is kind of emasculating.
Well, then, you'd better
make up for it in a minute.
♪ I'm gonna see your dick ♪
Sorry.
- ♪ I'm gonna fucking see it ♪
- Yeah, OK. Yeah...
What if there is no scrutiny,
it's just putting us
together in any old order,
and we all go along with it
'cause they're always
telling us how clever it is?
Yeah, but it does put
people with the one.
It's got a 99.8% success rate.
But how do you know
they're perfect matches?
I mean, what if all it's actually
doing is gradually wearing us down,
putting us in one
relationship after another
for random durations
in a random sequence?
Each time you get a little bit more
pliable, a little bit more broken,
until eventually it coughs up
the final offering and
says that's the one.
And by that point you are
so defeated and so exhausted
that you just accept it, you settle.
And then you have to
live the rest of your life
convincing yourself you didn't.
Well done. That's one of the
bleakest things I've ever heard.
Thank you.
Right. Do you wanna know my theory?
Let's assume the system isn't random.
- It's as sophisticated as they say it is.
- OK.
Right, so using these, it slurps
up all your reactions, yeah?
- It builds up a complex profile.
- Mm-hmm.
Every crazy thought you've ever had,
all your dreams and
your weaknesses and...
- And your mad theories.
- Yeah, like, everything in your head.
- Right.
- So if it's everything in your head...
- does it have thoughts?
- All right, so now you're gonna say:
"What if that's us
and we're stuck in a simulation?"
Well, how would we know?
I think that settles it.
I might have been programmed to go "Ow."
OK.
- Hey, come here.
- No.
- Coach?
- Hello, Frank.
- I've gotta know.
- What would you like to know?
The expiry date for me and
Amy. I need to know how long.
You're not gonna talk me out of it?
Would you like me to talk you out of it?
Yeah. Uh... No. I...
Don't know.
No, I'm not gonna do
it. I said I wouldn't.
We shook on it.
Fuck it.
Recalibrating.
Coach?
- Coach.
- Recalibrating.
What's happening? Coach,
it's getting shorter.
One-sided observation has
destabilized the expiry date.
- What?
- One-sided observation
has destabilized the expiry date.
Recalibrating.
'Cause I looked at it on
my own, it made it shorter?
- That is correct.
- Why?
Everything happens for a reason.
All right, well, undo
it, then. Make it go back.
I cannot do that. Recalibrating.
What if she looks at it?
Once shortened, the expiry
date cannot be extended.
Why?
Everything happens for a reason.
- Come on. Come on.
- Recalibrating.
- When will it stop?
- It will stabilize
once recalibration has
completed. Recalibrating.
Stop it. Stop it. Just...
You OK?
Yeah, I'm fine.
- All right.
- I'm good.
Have you ever had more
than four or less than four?
What you thinking about?
Nothing.
All right, seriously, what's up?
- I looked.
- Looked at what?
We promised we wouldn't. We shook on it.
- Don't you wanna know what it said?
- No. That was the point.
- It's almost done anyway.
- How almost done?
We've got, like, an hour.
Why didn't you tell me this before?
- Didn't wanna spoil today.
- And this hasn't spoilt it?
It was supposed to be
five years, but now...
I looked at it, something
happened, it started going down.
- I don't know what it was.
- So you broke it?
No, no, no, no, no. I mean,
I don't... I don't know.
Why did you have to look at it?
Look, I was thinking maybe
we could overcome it somehow.
Why did you have to look at it?
Because I like you.
Like properly, really, I like you.
- For fuck's sake. And that wasn't enough?
- That's not the point.
- I looked, but that's not the issue here.
- Are you sure about that?
You're more wound up about
that than how short the time is.
Yes, because we had agreed.
Listen. Listen. Listen.
- What if we just ignore it?
- We can't.
Listen, we'll just fuck
the system. We'll fuck it...
- And do what?
- We'll jump out, over the wall, get out.
- There is nothing out there.
- How d'you know? How d'you know?
- Amy...
- You've ruined this.
You've ruined it.
Hey, it's nothing.
- Amy.
- Don't follow me.
Amy, I'm sorry.
Amy.
- Everything happens for a reason.
- What reason?
The system will be
assessing your reaction
to the painful premature termination
of a treasured relationship
and will adjust and improve its profile
of your eventual chosen one accordingly.
- You're a great comfort.
- Thank you.
I swear to God, I feel like
scaling the wall out there
and jumping in the fucking wilderness.
That would contravene
the rules of the system.
Oh, the fucking system.
Failure to comply with the
system may result in banishment.
All right, I know.
Christ, will you let me be angry
at least? Will you give me that?
You must vacate your
current living quarters
when the time expires.
Like I didn't know.
And if I hadn't have looked,
we'd have been together years.
She was...
You know when you meet someone
and you just know? You just know that...
Reckon you could pop this in me
now? I've sort of got jaw ache.
Yeah, come on.
And after all that, he never
even apologized, not once.
That's too bad.
Do you mind if I think about her?
If I can think about him?
Yeah, sound.
One, two, three, four.
Congratulations, Amy. Your
ultimate match has been identified.
Your pairing day is tomorrow.
- Ultimate as in "the one"?
- That is correct.
- And we meet tomorrow?
Tomorrow you'll be coupled
with your ultimate match
and together you will
leave this place forever.
OK.
Are you allowed to tell
me anything about them?
- Do I know them already?
- Negative.
- Right.
- There is one more thing.
Yeah, and what's that?
Prior to pairing day,
you have been allocated
a short farewell period
with an individual of your choosing.
A farewell period? Like, I
get to say goodbye to someone?
That is correct.
Data shows this can help
provide psychological closure.
Frank, I choose Frank.
Your choice has been registered.
Wait. Where are we meeting?
Usual booth, 7:30 p.m.
Right.
- Coach?
- Yes, Amy?
Count to four.
One, two, three, four.
Wait, wait. How long have we got?
Look, the system's set my
pairing day for tomorrow.
- Yeah, me too.
- Right.
I don't want whoever the
system reckons the one is, OK?
- I want you.
Failure to comply with the system
- may result in banishment.
- You can fuck off.
Can you remember where you
were before you came here?
You can't, can you?
- No.
- Me neither.
- Why can't I think of that?
- It's a test.
Do you remember the first night
that we were together? How did you feel?
I felt safe, happy, comfortable.
It felt right.
It felt like something locked
into place, like we'd met before.
Like it had happened before
and it'll happen again,
like it's happened a thousand
times over and over again.
- Do you know what I mean?
- Yeah. Yeah, I do.
Ever since we've met, this
world has been toying with us.
It's trying to keep us apart. It's...
It's a test, I swear it is,
and the two of us rebelling together
is something to do with passing it.
We've gotta fuck it all off.
Exactly. We've just gotta fuck
the whole thing off and go.
- Yeah, over the wall.
- Right over it.
- No matter what's out there.
- OK.
So let's go.
Yeah, let's go.
Come on.
♪ Burn down the disco ♪
♪ Hang the blessed DJ ♪
♪ Because the music ♪
♪ That they constantly play ♪
♪ It says nothing to me about my life ♪
♪ Hang the blessed DJ ♪
♪ Because the music
they constantly play ♪
♪ On the Leeds side-streets ♪
♪ That you slip down ♪
♪ The provincial towns you jog 'round ♪
♪ Hang the DJ, hang
the DJ, hang the DJ ♪
♪ Hang the DJ, hang the DJ ♪
♪ Hang the DJ, hang
the DJ, hang the DJ ♪
♪ Hang the DJ, hang the DJ ♪
♪ Hang the DJ, hang
the DJ, hang the DJ ♪
♪ Hang the DJ, hang the DJ ♪
♪ Hang the DJ, hang
the DJ, hang the DJ ♪
♪ Hang the DJ, hang the DJ ♪
♪ Hang the DJ, hang
the DJ, hang the DJ ♪
♪ Hang the DJ, hang the DJ ♪
♪ Hang the DJ, hang
the DJ, hang the DJ ♪
♪ Hang the DJ ♪
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -