Liam Foxwell, welcome.
Thank you.
OK, little speech time.
I've mentioned this to
everyone about their appraisals,
and I just want you to know that this
isn't a witch-hunt for the deadwood.
It is much more of a...
treasure hunt for the gold?
Shit sinks.
But also, cream floats.
Yes, yes, I see that.
A new the area we're
getting lots of play in...
and your office could
be at the centre for...
is litigation in
retrospective parenting cases.
Retrospective...
Bobby sues Mum and Dad
for insufficient attention
leading to lack of confidence,
leading to damages against earnings.
Right, and we're OK,
the firm's OK with that, ethically?
And morally?
Yep.
Sure.
Yeah, yeah, right.
Are you?
Totally, yeah.
Yes.
OK, Liam, look,
so if we invite you to stay with
the firm in the new environment,
what we'd have you do is
pull an exhaustive redo
with personnel, maybe... next week.
Well, I was ready to do
a big redo right now, but...
No, it's fine, next week's fine.
But I have to ask you this...
they're not going to hit anything
to freak us out, are they?
There's no major
deletions this quarter?
No, no, everything's
well within... parameters.
Great, OK, Liam,
this has been really great.
Look, really hope to... look
forward to seeing you again.
OK, thank you.
Airport, please.
'Live...
'breathe...
'smell.
'Of a daily cup of coffee, and
three decades of backup for free.
'In-store ingrain procedure
with local anaesthetic
'and you're good to go.
'Because memory is for living.'
OK, great,
this has been really great, Liam,
we really hope to... look forward
to seeing you again.
We really hope to... look forward
Sorry!
Mr Foxwell.
Could you just rewind me
your last 24 hours for me, please?
Great, and back that up for me
times 64 for the week.
That's great.
Enjoy your flight, Mr Foxwell.
I'm not being funny,
right, but look at that.
Look at what?
That!
Frayed carpet, there, you see?
Seriously?
Yes, seriously!
This is a five-star suite.
I pay good money
to have perfect details.
Now I've got that shitty
carpet for the rest of my life.
Only if you keep looking at it,
mate.
Thanks, Jonas!
Fuck off.
All right, now, you thought the
carpet was bad, have a look at this.
You've met Lucy, my wife,
at the Dublin wedding?
That's right, yes, hi, Liam.
Hi... Hi again.
Hello.
Lucy... Liam,
we met at the Dublin wedding.
Liam!
Great.
Liam, yes.
Come in.
Thank you.
- Great to see you again.
- Yeah, you too.
Where's Fi been hiding you?
You know, in our house.
We didn't know... well, she didn't
know if you would make it.
It was over quicker than I thought.
Sorry, hello.
Let's get you a drink.
Beer OK?
Lovely, thank you.
Everyone's through there,
so I'll be in in a minute, OK?
OK, thank you.
Hi.
You're back early, then,
I didn't think you'd make it.
Yeah, I didn't stay over and I
caught an early flight back, so...
- Hi.
- Hello.
So, how was the appraisal?
Well, they said they'd let me do
a redo sometime next week, so...
But good?
Well...
- Later?
- Later.
OK.
- How's Jody?
- At home, Gina's babysitting.
Hey.
Jonas, this is...
- Liam...
- Jonas.
Dude, it's really nice to meet you.
- You all right?
- Good, thank you.
- And you know Jeff?
- Yes.
Yeah, you remember meeting Jeff,
because he'd have shown you,
I don't know, a redo
of the side of his fridge.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
piss off, Jonas.
- Hello.
Your wife's being
very mean to me tonight.
Well she's like that.
Yeah, tell me about it.
- You all right for a drink?
- I'm fine, thank you, Jonas.
Lynn, come and meet Liam, he's...
A soon-to-be
unemployed/unemployable lawyer.
And Jeff.
Jeff and Fi...
used to run the parties down
the Fraser Road with Paul and me.
Mad old days.
Before we started up the Kings.
So, yeah...
So, Liam, what was it you had,
an assessment?
Appraisal.
How'd it go?
Good.
Well, it was a disaster,
but you know, I don't know.
- Hard to gauge?
- Yeah
Let's have a look.
Redo, we can
appraise the appraisal.
Yeah, great.
Throw it up there
and we can grade you.
Come on...
It could be fun, we could...
vote!
- Paul?
- Yeah?
I work in recruitment,
so it might be quite useful for you.
Right, OK.
Liam's redoing his
appraisal so we can give him marks.
- Notes.
- Pointers, you know.
- I think Liam would probably...
- Yes, do you know what...
Guys, no, come on,
seriously, that's not cool,
I mean Liam's
obviously uncomfortable,
so let's just drop it, yeah?
Have a cool time.
Time to eat!
It's ready.
Thank you so much
for inviting us this evening.
It's been too long, too long.
Fi.
I haven't met him before, have I?
Jonas, is it?
He's one of the old crowd.
I think I said.
- You OK?
- Yeah, yeah.
- You know, if you're not in the mood,
we can go. - No, no, I'm fine.
Sure?
Hey!
Sync and corrected by APOLLO Resync
for WEB-DL by Darleg www.addic7ed.com
Yeah! I brought enough
for others to share.
Thank you.
I've, been cooking a lot
since the break-up.
Jonas has had a tough one.
Was it bad?
Yeah.
Yeah, we were in the middle
of planning is all
and I suddenly realised that
the less the relationship means
the more you spend
on the wedding, you know!
You actually start obsessing over
the tiniest little details,
like the thickness
of the wedding invitation paper
because, I mean, God knows you need
something to fucking talk about!
So, everybody, this is Helen.
Helen, Jonas.
- Hi.
And everyone!
- Hi!
- Help yourself.
Jonas was just explaining why
relationships are a sham.
Are they? Shit!
They're like going
to the theatre, OK?
You pay loads to go and ultimately
you are wasting your entire night,
so, when someone asks you,
"Did you have a good time?",
you both say,
"Yeah! Yeah, it was great."
The problem is the
more that you pay
and the longer it goes on, the more
you're, "Yeah, we loved it!",
you know, "We love being together
and never fucking anyone else"
"and only just having
one other person"
"to share our real thoughts with for
our entire lives, yeah, it's great!"
Would you say you loved her, though?
I just think we just really fancied
each other and that was what it was.
You know what it's like early on.
You know, we were just,
I don't know,
we were just two tools
in the tool shed
that just fit together
really fucking well.
I mean, still, by the end, I'd
be like, "Go on, honey, you go up,"
"I'm just going to watch
a little bit more of the news"
and I'd find myself, you know,
watching redos of, like,
hot times in earlier relationships!
Easy!
I'm just saying, there's
a beautiful woman upstairs,
you know, waiting
to have sex with me.
What, right now?
She's upstairs, you know,
waiting to have sex with me
and I'm sat downstairs watching
redos of, like, some hot times
with some hot girl that I just
picked up in some place
and I'm fucking pulling
myself off. I mean, seriously?
Come on...
Come on, guys.
I mean, we all scroll
through the Grain
rifling through our greatest hits
for a little bit of filth
now and then, surely?
Not me.
Helen doesn't have a Grain!
No shit!
Was that a political thing?
No, no, I was gouged
about 12 months ago.
Jesus, was that painful?
Total agony.
But on the plus of that, I don't
remember it that clearly.
There's a scar on here.
Yeah, can I...?
Yeah, that feels quite nice.
Yeah, no brain damage, clearly!
Well, my sight held on fine, so...
So, who took it then?
Stolen to order,
as far as they could tell,
probably to some millionaire
Chinese perve.
Really?! Yeah.
Is that for real?
Yeah, and none of
it was encrypted, so...
So, they saw the lot!
The thing is, after I was gouged
I didn't have one for a few days
and then just kind of, liked it.
It's cool.
That's cool.
I mean, because more people are...
I mean, now, right?
Like, going Grainless?
I believe it's huge with hookers.
I mean, no offence!
No, no, it's OK. Sure, I...
Well, I'm pretty boring.
One man is a time.
Serial monogamist.
I'm a serial monogamist.
I'm staying faithful
to my cornflakes right now!
Well, I think it's an interesting
choice, going Grainless.
It's a brave choice.
I'm sorry, but I...
I couldn't do it.
OK, I was going to play some redos
from the Fraser O days.
Stuff from last night,
depressing and fun.
You know half the organic
memories you have a junk,
just not trustworthy.
Colleen works in Grain development.
With half the population you can
implant false memories,
just by asking leading
questions in therapy.
You can make people
remember getting lost
in shopping malls they
never visited,
getting bothered by paedophile
babysitters they never had.
I'm just happier now.
'OK, great, Liam, this has been,
this has been really great...
'we really hope to look
forward to seeing you again.'
He looks forward to seeing
you again, that's good.
"Hopes" to look forward.
'We really hope to look
forward to seeing you again.'
It's phoney.
Hang on.
Pause it.
Now backup.
Zoom in there.
Come on, that's a tick.
That could be a V or an L.
- It's a tick!
- Or the start of the swastika.
It's probably the start of the
swastika, they were such pricks!
- Did you have fun with the old gang?
- Yeah.
D'you speak to that Jonas much?
No, no, not really.
He's a bit of a knob, ain't he?
Bit of a dick?
Jonas.
Pulling himself off to his own
relationship theories.
It must be such a drag,
Jonas, putting it about!
And when he protected me
from those arseholes,
"Hey, come on, guys,"
"it's really not cool to redo
another man's appraisals, dudes."
Then why invite him over?
I like him.
You wanted me to invite him.
I didn't say anything.
You were laughing
at everything he said.
You invited him!
It was obvious
I didn't want him to come.
'It's only, it's early
to call it a night.'
'Do fancy a quick one down the pub?'
'We've got to get back,
'rescue Jodie from
the paedophile babysitter!
'Yeah.'
'But why don't you come back to
ours, for a nightcap if you want?'
See?
It was obvious I didn't want him to
come, I was being polite to a moron.
If you really don't want to come,
you can get rid of him.
Hey, hey!
Hey.
Well, actually, what time is it?
It's midnight.
Shit, it's quite late,
time's gone on.
Yeah, time does that.
15 minutes.
Yeah.
But we've got the babysitter
inside, so...
So, is that new info?
No, it's just that we, I mean,
we thought, right, Fi?
Yeah. Yeah.
OK, no, I get it.
No, it's just that, actually,
it turns out we're tired
and I guess we forgot,
but now we've remembered, so...
Sorry.
No, it's fine, really.
I'm sorry.
It's cool, no worries.
I've got a back-up plan, so...
Cool, well, we vote the back-up.
Yeah, I will do.
See you later, Fi.
It was good to meet you, man.
Yeah.
Nice one.
Brilliant. Brilliant.
OK, cool.
Good to meet you, man.
Yeah.
Listen, Gina, it's a 40-minute
wait for a cab, but if you want,
I have the bed made up in my office.
OK, thanks, Fi.
Hey, there's just, you know, use
anything. There's T-shirts and...
Yeah, thanks, I'll show myself out.
All right, night.
Night, guys.
Night, Gina.
Thank you.
'Bye-bye.
'OK.
'Love you, love you.'
Was he a big part of the gang?
Who? Jonas?
I don't know, yeah?
Let me guess, he'd spent his time
oozing round the girls,
offering backrubs.
Not really.
Circling for an orifice.
Was he always that oily or...
OK, look.
What?
It's nothing, but...
You may have noticed a bit
of an atmosphere because...
me and Jonas, years ago,
had a bit of a thing.
You had a thing with oily dude man?
It was just a little thing
and I didn't even know
you back then, so...
You slept with oily dude man?
That's hilarious!
We've all got our skeletons,
how about you and Gemma?
What, I told you about Gemma.
Gemma was a nutcase...
But you never mentioned Jonas.
I did, I told you I hooked up
with someone in Marrakech.
Jonas is Mr Marrakesh?!
It was a stupid thing...
I thought Mr Marrakech was some
sort of super cool...
Not him.
It was years ago and...
Are you embarrassed by that?
Cos it's embarrassing.
I'm sorry, but, Christ,
are you not embarrassed?
It was years ago.
But you dated him for a month?
That's what I said.
Cos when you told me about
Mr Marrakech, it was a week.
No, I didn't.
Pah!
'What about you?'
I don't want to see our
first time right now.
Syou're about to talk.
'I went away and had a little thing
that did my head in for a while
'with this, sort of...
'..this, sort of, headfuck
that I met in Marrakech.'
'Mr Marrakech?'
'Yeah.'
'I'm imagining a chillum
and a big knob.'
'No, it was like dormouse.'
'Big deal, big heart-breaker?'
'No, it was just a week.
'It was a weird week.'
So, a weird week or a month?
The point is, it wasn't a big deal.
Well, it was big enough
to do your head in.
Jonas, King Dormouse-Dick
of Marrakech did your head in!
That was a nice night, used to be.
You're getting obsessed.
I'm not.
We had all this with Dan, I don't
want you going like that again.
He had little creepy beady eyes
and he was always...
What? Acting like
he was interested?
And you know what, I think
he probably did fancy me
and actually he wasn't
completely hideous,
so in another life I don't know,
but nothing happened!
And Jonas...
he's an old fling.
So what? Don't go all fucked up!
What, I'm fucked up, am I?
No, I mean, just...
No, no, no, that's brilliant,
sometimes you're a bitch.
I didn't mean that.
'You're a bitch!'
I'd like you to erase that.
Also, "sometimes".
You can't just edit off
the word, "sometimes"!
I'm sorry, Fi, I know I go a bit
weird and wonky sometimes.
- I love you, you know?
- I know.
'..In a toolshed that just fit
together really fucking well,
'but still by the end I'd be like,
"Go, on, you go to bed, honey,
'"I'm just going to catch a little
bit more of the news,"
'and then I'd find myself, you know,
watching redos of hot times
'in earlier relationships.
'I've got a beautiful woman upstairs
waiting to have sex with me.
'And I'd find myself, you know,
watching redos of hot times
'in earlier relationships.'
'Easy!'
'Lip read reconstruction enabled.
- 'Hey, it's good to see you.
- 'Good to see you, too.
'I was nervous when I heard you
were going to be here.
'It's weird, isn't it?'
- Morning.
- Gina, over here.
Come here a second.
I just want your opinion.
It's just a silly game.
Sit down.
Answer this.
I'm a serial monogamist.
I'm staying faithful
to my corn flakes right now.
Now, is that funny?
There's no need to be nice,
the man's a prick.
Is that funny, in your opinion?
Well...
I'm a serial monogamist.
I'm staying faithful
to my corn flakes right now.
- No?
- No
- I don't know.
- You do.
Morning.
What's this?
I'm just getting Gina's
opinion on something.
I'm a serial monogamist.
I'm staying faithful
to my corn flakes right now.
I was just wondering because you
found it funny, but it isn't,
and Gina agrees.
I don't really want to get involved.
Let me get you a cab.
My dad's on his way.
Just one other thing.
We both want him to come back,
but who wants him to come back more?
Off the top of your head,
who wants him to come back more?
OK, well, bye.
Yeah, bye.
It's early. It's early
to call it a night.
Fancy a quick one down the pub?
Got to get back, rescue Jodie
from the paedophile baby-sitter.
That's just a...
That's a joke.
Sorry.
Jonas, why don't you come back to
ours for a nightcap, if you want?
Yeah.
Now, ignore the joke. Who's
more keen for him to come back?
I don't know.
You do know, Gina.
I'm so sorry, he's really hungover.
That's OK.
I'm staying faithful to
my corn flakes right now.
That is just objectively not funny.
Anyone would say,
"That's not funny."
That was fucking embarrassing.
Whatever you're queuing up, stop it.
Sit down, please.
You see that?
You know Geoff?
Yeah, you remember me and Geoff,
because he would have shown you
a re-do of the side of his fridge,
something like that.
- Spot the difference.
- You're drunk.
I'm the difference.
He's the greatest guy in the world
and then I arrived and... you clam.
For clarity.
We're just talking!
But moments later, you're so stiff.
I don't know, a re-do...
You don't know how
to stand around him.
Your gauges are all over the place,
hot and cold.
This is just stupid!
You can't hide it.
Not completely.
See how you look at him.
The less the relationship means,
the more you spend on the wedding.
Really, you start obsessing
about these tiny little details
like the thickness
of the wedding invitation paper.
Now, how you look at me.
I think it's an interesting choice,
going grainless.
It's a brave choice.
I'm sorry, but...
Tell me you look at me nice
like you look at him. You can't.
And how am I looking
at you now, Liam?
How long did you go out
with him for?
Does it matter?
You know, half the organic
memories you have are junk.
Just not trustworthy.
When it comes to little things.
And big ones.
Is that Marrakesh?
Does that look like Marrakesh?
No.
It's not Marrakesh.
So, how long did you
go out with him for?
All right, about six months.
So not a week or a month.
Six months.
The ever-inflating romance.
You're probably still
going out with him.
Why am I on trial here?
What's been going on?
Nothing has been going on.
It was... Christ, you know how it
is when you first get with someone
and then previous
boyfriends come up.
He was never a boyfriend,
he was always a weird week.
I downplayed it.
I fudged it, it was...
You lied.
Not everything that
isn't true is a lie, Liam.
Hello?
So he was a bigger thing than I made
out and, yeah, he's sort of a dick.
Sort of? He's a massive...
I liked him then.
And I don't like him,
not like that, not now.
So, just to get this clear.
He fucks you, gets footage
for his redo wank file,
but you're still pally.
This is sad!
- Cos if he was...
- This is just sad!
He probably sits there
and tosses himself
off all over his
cashmere blanket.
It was years ago!
Not for him.
I'd find myself watching
redos of really hot times
early in relationships.
'Easy.'
Sober up.
Make yourself puke.
Whatever, I don't care.
Just sort this out.
Fuck.
I'd find myself watching
redos of really hot times
early in relationships.
Easy.
And I'm downstairs watching
some redo of some night
I've picked up somebody else and...
Yeah, nice, Geoff. She's upstairs
waiting to have sex with me
and I'm downstairs watching
some redo
of some night I've picked
up somebody else.
Easy.
And I'm fucking pulling myself off.
I'm just saying.
'Green warning.
'Grain assistant suggests
you may not be in a suitable
'physical condition for the activity
you appear to be engaged in.
'To override,
continue at your own risk.
'All health and personal
accident insurance is... '
Thank you.
- 'Who's that?'
- It's Liam.
Liam from last night.
'Liam. Is Fi with you?'
She's not, no.
'Sorry, Liam, mate,
is there something that you want?'
Yeah, I just want to
come in and talk to you.
Can you open the gate?
- Yeah, sure.
- I'll let you in.
Nice one, nice one.
- Hey.
What do you want?
I just want to come in
for a bit, dude.
That looks expensive.
Is that expensive?
Look, Liam, it's morning, mate.
Fucking hell. Liam.
Jonas, this is a nice place!
Hey. Seriously, man, it's not cool
you just walking in like this.
To be honest with you,
it's a little bit weird.
Is that a Marrakeshian lamp?
Liam, do I have to call Fi?
Did you guys have a row
or something like that?
- Sit down.
- No, I'm all right.
Go on, sit down. It's not
a bear trap, it's a chair.
Do you want me to bounce this
off your fucking head?
I'm joking, Jonas.
Bloody hell, I thought you were
supposed to be cool, man.
I thought you were meant
to be fucking brilliant.
What's going on?
Yeah, figures.
Get some good stuff
for the scrapbook?
I think you should go.
I don't blame you.
I would have.
Tell you what, let's have a look.
Go on, chuck it
on the screen, don't be shy!
Come on!
I'm fucking joking again, Jonas!
For goodness' sake,
you need to grow a sense of humour.
- He's uptight, isn't he?
- OK, Liam.
- It's a lovely room, this.
- Thank you.
Is this where you masturbate
to images of my wife?
- Or do you do it in that room?
- OK, Liam, I want you to leave now.
Do you sometimes start in here
and then finish in there?
The world's pretty much your oyster,
isn't it?
I want you to leave.
Well, that's a pity.
- Come on, mate.
- All right, now, what are you doing?
Don't do that.
Come on now!
- What are you doing?
- Jesus! Get out!
- Stand up, Jonas, come on!
Hey.
What do you want?
Don't do that.
Come on, Danny!
- 'What are you doing?
'Jesus! Get out, you fucking prick.
'Tell you what... '
Stop it!
I tell you what you're going to do.
You're going to get every bit
of Fion you've got in there
and you're going to select it
all and you're going to wipe it!
Hello, police, I'm witnessing
a serious assault at five...
'Wipe it!
'Fuck off.
'I don't have a brain chip
to show you.'
This is a bottle, right?
Either you wipe it or
I will fucking gouge you myself.
Jesus!
OK.
Just do what he says.
Not on your eye, in there.
On there!
He's doing it!
Now, delete it all.
The lot!
Or I will crack your skull
and I will gouge your fucking neck.
I'm doing it.
Stay away from my house!
'Now, delete it all.
The lot!
'Or I will crack your skull
and I will gouge your fucking neck.
'I'm doing it.'
Liam?
Where did you go?
What happened?
Liam, what happened?
Did you use a condom or not?
Just say.
Liam, whatever you think...
Am I Jodie's father?
- Liam!
- Am I?
Yes, of course.
- You sure about that?
- Yes!
That's nice.
I always liked that picture,
didn't you?
It's why I bought it for you.
I never liked it.
Thought it was pretentious shit.
'I'll tell you what you're
going to do.
'You're going to get every
bit of Fion... '
' Christ, what have you done?
'Select it all... '
We're getting to the good bit.
'Hello, police, I'm witnessing
a serious assault at... '
'Now, delete it all.
The lot!
'Or I will crack your skull
and I will gouge your fucking neck.'
18 months ago in this room.
You know when you suspect something,
it's always better
when it turns out to be true.
It's like I've had a bad tooth
for years and I'm just finally
getting my tongue in there and I'm
digging out all the rotten shit.
That's not what it looks like.
This did Jonas come round
to read you a story?
No, it was...
A story about fucking?
It was...
When all the Dan stuff was going on
and you'd walked out.
For like ten minutes.
For five days, Liam.
No call, no nothing.
So you fucked him after four days?
That's heroic.
I mean, three days,
that's admirable, but four days?
I mean, you must have been gagging.
I was so upset.
We went for a drink, I got drunk.
It shouldn't have happened.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry,
I can't say anything else.
I love you.
Did you use a condom?
Yes.
Cos we didn't have any here.
We were trying.
He had some.
In his pocket?
In his car.
Was it his decision,
or did you make him wear one?
I made him.
- And you saw him put it on?
- Yes.
Show me, then.
Show me on there.
I need to see it, Fi.
I deleted it.
I wanted it to go away,
I wiped the whole thing.
- Did you?
- Yeah.
So there's just a blank
gap in your timeline?
Yeah.
Show me that, then.
Yeah, OK.
I have to find it.
No! No deleting it, not now.
No, no.
It's still on there, is it?
I'm sorry.
You have to show it to me, Fi.
Why?
Cos I want to see it.
I love you.
Show it to me.
No.
- Show it to me.
- No.
- Show it to me!
- No!
Show it to me! I want to see!
I want to see what he looks like!
This isn't me!
Look what you're doing to me!
Fi, I need to see it!
Please.
I need to see it, Fi.
'Hurry up.
'Sorry!'
I love you.
I know you do.
Hello, stinky!
Hey.
Brown or green?
Green?
Sync and corrected by APOLLO Resync
for WEB-DL by Darleg www.addic7ed.com